roxy-europe.com 2012-06-15

# Roxy : Help Desk

We, Quiksilver, Inc. (referred to herein as "Roxy," "we," "us" and "our"), are strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all of our users and subscribers while offering the highest quality user experience to them. Because we gather certain types of information about and from you, our users and subscribers, in order to fulfill your requests and better serve your needs, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of this information. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather, how we use it, how to correct or change it, and what steps we take to safeguard personal information provided to us both online and offline. Please read the complete Privacy Policy below, as well as our Terms of Use, and contact us if you have any questions.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU?**

You can use [www.roxy.com](http://www.roxy.com/) or our affiliate websites, (collectively, the "Website") without having an account. You can visit the Website, read articles and other materials, browse merchandise, and check on offerings without giving us any personally identifiable information. You can also contact us about a particular video, picture, audio file or other posting without having an account. Certain other activities on the Website, such as posting comments or product reviews and signing up to receive e-mail updates from Roxy and our affiliates and partners, do not require you to register for an account, but may require that you provide certain personal information such as your name and/or e-mail address. Still other activities, including purchasing products through the Website, require you to register for a user account. To register, you must create a user account, which requires you to provide your e-mail address and select a password. The password you select is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.

Whether or not you register, in order to provide users and subscribers with the most efficient and enhanced personalized service and attention, we may request information about you in certain circumstances and collect certain information automatically. We also use contact lists and other information which are obtained from third-parties. For the convenience of all of our customers and to better serve you, we create and maintain a customer account that includes all the collected personal information we may have with respect to an individual. You can update or correct your contact information or change your preferences about receiving offers and information from us at any time, including changing your preferences about sharing information with third-parties.

This Privacy Policy also applies to your use of any Roxy page, platform or application owned, manager or run by a third party, subject to such third party's applicable policies. 

**Information You Volunteer**

We collect personally identifiable information that you volunteer to us (such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, age, gender, hobbies, family information and/or similar demographic information), when you subscribe to, or create an account with, the Website, place an order through the Website (see the section below for more information on subscriptions, account management and orders), enter a contest or sweepstakes through the Website, request a catalog or voluntarily register on the Website. Often this additional information is optional or requested anonymously in connection with a survey. Website visitors may register to receive our e-mail updates, participate in surveys, or enter online contests and sweepstakes. Registration may also be required to purchase products through the Website and participate in certain other features made available on our Website. Sometimes registration can be accomplished by submitting only an e-mail address and password. Other offerings may require the submission of additional information. For example, our Website may ask which disciplines you enjoy most, surfing, skating or snowboarding. Registration forms will indicate what information is required and what information (if any) is optional.

**Information Collected Automatically**

We may also automatically collect certain other information, including but not necessarily limited to, your IP and referring Website addresses, browser type, domain name and Website access times. This information helps facilitate your online experience on our Website. In addition, we use cookies to track usage patterns on our Website and to control the display of ads, as well as to offer other functionalities (such as screening for age, helping to track items in your shopping basket at websites which offer online shopping opportunities, and "recognizing" you to speed up your log-in when you visit our Website). You can turn off cookies, but that will affect your online experience and you may not be able to complete an order or transaction. Please see below for more detail on cookies.

**Other Information**

We conduct market research so that we can continually improve our brands and our Website and may purchase or rent lists of potential subscribers or customers from third-parties. Those lists may include information on current subscribers or customers. This information may be included in our database in order to help us serve you better by, for example, minimizing multiple mailings and e-mailings and providing information tailored to your interests.

**Publicly available information**

The name you provide (not your e-mail address) is displayed to other users when you post a comment or product review via our Website. Remember that any comments, product reviews or other information you post is publicly available. Any comments, product reviews or other information that you post or submit to the Website may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

**WHAT DO WE DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?**

We use information you provide to fulfill your requests and improve our Website, products and services. We may, from time to time, produce reports for advertisers, sponsors and vendors containing anonymous, aggregate information about our users and subscribers, such as demographic, age and online usage information. This information allows us to provide content and offers that are most relevant to our users and subscribers and to work more closely with advertisers. We do not include any personally identifiable information of our users in these reports.

We use personal information so that we may display or send custom, personalized content to our Website visitors and send newsletters, mail, e-mails, features, promotional material, surveys and other updates, information or offers to our users and subscribers. From time to time, we may also establish business relationships with other persons or entities that we believe to be trustworthy and whose privacy policies are generally consistent with our privacy policy ("Choice Partners"). In such cases we might share and cross-reference information, including personal information about you that will enable our Choice Partners to contact you regarding products and services that you might find of interest.

To serve you better, we may also combine information you give us online, in our stores or through our catalogs. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information which we receive from our Choice Partners or other third-parties. We use the total mix of information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes as we determine from time to time.

A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information by going to the _unsubscribe_ page and following the instructions on those pages. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our products and services, fulfill customer requests, announce sweepstakes/contest winners, respond to any future problems, such as difficulties in navigating the Website or accessing certain features, and to gauge user trends to determine what products and services are most popular with users.

We allow users of the Website to send products, articles, videos, pictures or links by e-mail to other parties who may be interested in them. We do not retain any e-mail addresses (unless you are a member who has already voluntarily provided your e-mail address) of either the sender or recipient of such articles or links after they are sent, and we do not share "send a friend" e-mail addresses with third-parties. We also allow users of the Website to share products, articles, videos, pictures or links through certain third-party websites. We provide such links for your reference and convenience only. A link from the Website to a third-party Website does not mean or imply that Roxy endorses the content on that third-party Website or the operator or operations of that third-party Website.

Of course, we use personal information to allow you to subscribe online or to make product purchases on our Website. We and our technical and fulfillment agents, partners and consultants follow carefully proscribed procedures to safeguard credit card data in connection with your transactions and adhere to certain legal requirements.

**HOW DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Personal information is available to Roxy and the technical and fulfillment agents, partners and consultants who make our Website, products and services available to you. Anonymous information is available to our advertisers, sponsors and promotional and business partners. We share your personal information with third-parties only as described below.

**Roxy and Its Agents**

Roxy may access anonymous, aggregate demographic data and any personal information you provide for internal marketing purposes, including sending you notices of sweepstakes winners, new websites, services or products we offer and any other orders. To facilitate subscriptions, catalog requests and orders, Roxy will cache your order information, and create an authorization with a merchant account (e.g., your credit card company). Website hosting firms, technical and database consultants, advertising agencies, order processing partners, customer service partners and fulfillment firms, including firms assisting us in offering contests, sweepstakes and promotions, may have access to personally identifiable information in the course of making our products and services available. All companies working for and with Roxy must comply with our privacy policies, and are not permitted to sell your information to third-parties or to use it except as authorized by us and you, or as permitted or required by law.

**Participating Vendors**

We may offer opportunities to make purchases online from special participating vendors. If we do so, we will also give participating manufacturers, retailers, wholesalers or distributors the order information and authorization for the merchant bank. Any time you order from a participating vendor, that vendor will automatically have all the information related to the order. Participating vendors have their own privacy policies, and they may use that information to advise you directly of other products and offerings that they provide. Roxy is not responsible for these third-parties' respective privacy policies, and we urge you to inquire about their information collection and use practices. In addition, all vendors will receive the same anonymous, aggregate data that our advertisers receive.

**Credit Card Companies**

As in any transaction, your credit card company will have all relevant information about the name of the vendor, item(s) purchased, date, total cost and other information necessary to process the transaction. Roxy will not otherwise provide any personal data to your credit card company without your permission.

**Advertisers, Sponsors and Promotional and Business Partners**

We share anonymous, aggregate demographic information (such as gender, age, income, hobbies, interests, etc.), and anonymous information obtained from cookies and similar technologies, with our advertisers, sponsors, promotional and business partners, and participating vendors. No personally identifiable information is disclosed to any of these third-parties in providing these reports. Credit card numbers, bank account numbers and passwords are not shared with advertisers, sponsors or promotional partners, and are only shared with the specific vendors with whom you place an online order.

Information which we obtain in non-Internet transactions or sweepstakes is handled differently. We may share offline contact information with third-parties, who may send you offers or information about their products or services. You must opt out if you do not wish to receive information from third-parties or us by mail.

Your e-mail address is not shared with third-parties unless you agree to receive information, by opting in, from third-parties. In other words, we may extend e-mail offers to users or subscribers on behalf of our business partners about a particular product or service that may be of interest to you, but only if you have indicated that you would like to receive these offers. If you wish to receive such offers, we will not share or disclose your name or e-mail address to those business partners, but will send you the information or offers on their behalf. As a result, although Roxy may receive a fee from our business partners for this service, Roxy sends the offers so that your personal information is never shared with any outside third-party. Of course, you may opt out of receiving these offers at any time.

Sometimes we will give you the opportunity to opt in to receive e-mail offers from third-parties not affiliated with Roxy. If you decide to accept these offers, we will provide, with your consent, your contact information to the third-party. On our Website, visitors will also have opportunities to sign up directly with certain advertisers and sponsors to enter contests or sweepstakes or to receive e-mail updates and other information directly from them. Third-party vendors and advertisers will also use technical and other consultants. We urge visitors to review carefully the privacy policies of these firms. Roxy is not responsible for the privacy policies and procedures of any third-party.

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information, personal or otherwise, online in any community area (whether through the Website or any other service available online), that information can be collected and used by others. For example, if you use chat, forums, bulletin boards, blogs or message boards, or if you post personal information online (such as your e-mail address), you may receive unsolicited messages from others. Roxy has no control over this use of your personal information.

**Important Note**

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent for the following purposes: as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our Website and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation.

**HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?**

Your web browser offers so-called "cookies" which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. However, cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best and make it easier to use the Website. We use a cookie in order to retain the contents of your shopping cart while you browse the Website. Cookies also enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser. Although our Website is viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features or offerings will not be available to you. Our third-party advertisers may also use cookies.

**HOW DO WE USE WEB BEACONS?**

Some pages on the Website may contain electronic images known as web beacons, which are also called "single-pixel gifs." These images allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to count how many messages have been opened and acted upon. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information but they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our Website usage. Web beacons collect only a limited range of information, including the time and date of page view, cookie number and description of the page on which the web beacon resides. Some of our web pages may also contain web beacons placed there by our advertising partners to help us determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.

**WHAT ABOUT THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS?**

Some of the third-party content displayed in our Website is provided by outside companies. This content may contain cookies and may also contain web beacons. Unlike cookies and web beacons used by Roxy in content we control on our Website, we do not have access to information collected from cookies or web beacons received in connection with third-party content. While we use third-parties which we believe are reputable to serve some or all of the content placed within our Website, third-parties may use information (not including personally identifiable information) about your visits to our Website to assist in serving their third-party content to you. They may also share anonymous information with their clients such as date/time of the content shown, the specific content shown, the IP address and other similar information.

**HOW CAN YOU CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

We believe that choice in how and when you are contacted is key to customer satisfaction. Therefore, we offer several ways for you to update your contact information and/or change your preferences.

  1. If you have a user account at our Website, you may be able to log on and update or change your contact or account information.
  2. You may unsubscribe to any of our e-mail updates by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any e-mail message.
  3. You may write to us and update your contact information or ask that we not share your personal contact information with third-parties at: Quiksilver, Inc., 15202 Graham Street, Huntington Beach, CA 92649, Attn: Privacy Coordinator. In those instances, we will retain your information in a "do not promote" file in our database. 
  4. You may also contact us via email at [privacypolicy@roxy.com](mailto:privacypolicy@roxy.com).

We will take commercially reasonable steps to implement your opt-out requests promptly; but you may still receive promotional information from us by mail for up to 60 days due to printing and mailing schedules, and up to 10 days for e-mail. You may also continue to receive information from those third-parties to whom your information was previously disclosed pursuant to their respective privacy policies.

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt important information, such as your credit card data, in an effort to prevent unauthorized access during transmission of your orders over the Internet. We incorporate standard industry practices internally and with our service providers, which we believe suits the degree of sensitivity of the information involved to maintain the security of your personal information and to avoid its disclosure except as described in this Privacy Policy. Your personal information may also be protected by the password you created when you registered for a user account at our Website. The confidentiality of any password is yours to protect. You may change it at anytime by following the instructions on the Website where you registered.

Although we have implemented systems and procedures to secure the data maintained by us, security during Internet transmissions can never be assured. Our policy is to limit access to personal data to those Roxy employees or agents with a specific need to access or retrieve this information. We store data on multiple service systems, in controlled environments. To maintain security, we conduct internal reviews of our security measures on a regular basis. Remember, however, that any personal information you post in comments, product reviews or elsewhere on the Website is available to anyone.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

The Website may include features or material that may be appealing to children under the age of 13. Roxy is strongly committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children who visit our Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under 13 and have adopted techniques to age-screen users on our Website to ensure compliance with this Privacy Policy and the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying regulations under United States federal law protect the privacy of children using the Internet. Our Website may include material and features that we believe to be unsuitable for children under 13 and which are not necessarily monitored. We encourage all parents to talk to their children about online safety and to monitor their children's use of the Internet.

**CHANGES IN CORPORATE STRUCTURE**

In developing our business, we may engage in the sale of certain assets and the company itself, or parts of it, may be sold, merged or otherwise transferred. In such transactions and changes in ownership, user information, whether personally identifiable or otherwise, may constitute one of the transferred assets. Roxy will notify affected users in accordance with the procedure for changing this Privacy Policy described below.

**VISITORS AND SUBSCRIBERS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

Our Website and the servers that make the Website available worldwide are located in the United States. The Internet laws in the United States govern all matters relating to the Website. Any information you provide in subscribing to our Website or registering or ordering at our Website will be transferred to the United States. By visiting our Website and submitting information, you authorize this transfer, processing and use. We adhere to the US-EU Safe Harbor Privacy Principles ("EU Safe Harbor") with respect to certain personally identifiable information that we receive from customers and employees in the European Union. Roxy has various other business units, service offerings and data collections which are not covered by this Privacy Policy, nor by Roxy's participation in the EU Safe Harbor, and Roxy makes no EU Safe Harbor representations with respect to any data collected or used in these business units, service offerings or data collections. For further background about the EU Safe Harbor, please refer to the U.S. Department of Commerce's Website at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to protect our users and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the Privacy Policy when you visit our Website to be sure that you are aware of and understand our current policy. If we make material changes to this policy, or in how we use or collect your personally identifiable information, we will prominently post such changes. We will not make any retroactive material changes in how we handle previously collected personal information unless you allow us to do so, or unless we are legally required to do so, and in such a case we will e-mail registered Website visitors information on material changes to this Privacy Policy. 

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please e-mail us at [privacypolicy@roxy.com](mailto:privacypolicy@roxy.com). Please include the URL of the Website and/or specific page within the Website involved in your request.

Or you can contact us by mail at:  
Quiksilver, Inc.  
15202 Graham Street  
Huntington Beach, CA 92649  
Attn: Privacy Coordinator

Or you can fax us at (714) 889-2325, Attn: Privacy Coordinator
